COMPUTER SCIENCE · COMPUTER ENGINEERING

□ (+82) 10-4126-1753 | ■ jaywonchung@snu.ac.kr | ♠ jaewonchung.me | 回 jaywonchung

### Summary.

I am a senior student majoring Electrical and Computer Engineering at Seoul National University, South Korea. I am interested in software systems that support deep learning workloads. I have experience on GPU cluster resource management, DNN computation offloading, and meta-learning. I also try to follow up on state-of-the-art deep learning research during my free time.

### Education

### **Seoul National University**

Seoul, South Korea

2015 - Present

B.S. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

• Current GPA: 4.09/4.3 (overall) 4.15/4.3 (major)

## Research Experience

Software Platform Lab SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN Apr 2020 - Present

- Working on Crane, an elastic GPU cluster resource manager.
- · Working with Professor Byung-Gon Chun.

#### **Virtual Machine and Optimization Lab**

SNU, South Korea

SENIOR PROJECT

Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

- Distributed DNN inference, Mobile Computing
- · Worked with Professor Soo-Mook Moon on developing a server-client collaborative DNN inference scheme.
- Proposed a distributed video DNN inference method that drastically reduces network traffic by exploiting intermittent knowledge distillation.
- Implemented the scheme with PyTorch and OpenMPI with an NVIDIA Jetson Nano embedded board as the client and conducted evaluation.

Computer Vision Lab SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

- Meta-learning, Few-shot Classification
- Conducted research on better meta-initialization points for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning (MAML) using an LSTM-based neural memory.
- Conducted research on generating task-aware class embeddings to augment feature maps of MAML by formulating a convex program (DPP).

#### **Lab of Imaging Science and Technology**

SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Deep Learning methods for Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping (QSM)
- Worked with Professor Jongho Lee and submitted our solution to the QSM challenge held by the 5th International Workshop on MRI Phase Contrast and QSM.
- · Designed, implemented, and trained a U-Net variant on in-vivo brain MRI field images and their COSMOS results.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

Deepest SNU, South Korea

MEMBER

Dec 2018 - Present

- · A free research group on all domains of deep learning. Aggregates researchers from both academia and industry with various backgrounds.
- Gained experience extensively in computer vision and meta-learning, and attended talks on computer vision, natural language processing, reinforcement learning, and speech recognition.
- Gave a talk with the title "Meta-Learning plus Memory".

#### **Coursera Global Translator Community**

translate-coursera.org

LANGUAGE COORDINATOR

Oct 2018 - Present

- · Served as Language Coordinator, a selected position that reviews and confirms works by other translators.
- Created Korean subtitles for Coursera Lectures initially provided only in English. Focused on courses related to machine learning.

# Teaching.

• Fall 2020 Computer Organization (Undergraduate architecture), Peer Tutor

Skills\_\_\_\_

**Programming** Python, PyTorch, C, Verilog, LaTeX, C++, CUDA, MATLAB, Go, JavaScript, Rust

**English** TOEFL 120 (Perfect score, Feb 2020), TOEIC 990 (Perfect score, Oct 2018), GRE 167/170/4.5 (Mar 2018)

## **Publications**

• ShadowTutor: Distributed Partial Distillation for Mobile Video DNN Inference, <u>Jae-Won Chung</u>, Jae-Yun Kim, Soo-Mook Moon, Proceedings of the 49th International Conference on Parallel Processing, 2020